nesmaairlines.com 2015-12-28

# Privacy Policy |

What information do we collect?

• We collect information from you when you place an order or subscribe to our newsletter.

• When ordering or registering on our site, as appropriate, you may be asked to enter your: name, e-mail address, mailing address, phone number or credit card information. You may, however, visit our site anonymously.

What do we use your information for?

Any of the information we collect from you may be used in one of the following ways:

• To process transactions. Your information, whether public or private, will not be sold, exchanged, transferred, or given to any other company for any reason whatsoever, without your consent, other than for the express purpose of delivering the purchased product or service requested.

• To administer a contest, promotion, survey or other site feature

• To send periodic emails. The email address you provide for order processing, may be used to send you information and updates pertaining to your order, in addition to receiving occasional company news, updates, related product or service information, etc. Note: If at any time you would like to unsubscribe from receiving future emails, we include detailed unsubscribe instructions at the bottom of each email.

How do we protect your information?  
• We implement a variety of security measures to maintain the safety of your personal information when you place an order or enter, submit, or access your personal information.

• We offer the use of a secure server. All supplied sensitive/credit information is transmitted via Secure Socket Layer (SSL) technology and then encrypted into our Payment gateway providers database only to be accessible by those authorized with special access rights to such systems, and are required to keep the information confidential.

Do we disclose any information to outside parties?  
We do not sell, trade, or otherwise transfer to outside parties your personally identifiable information. This does not include trusted third parties who assist us in operating our website, conducting our business, or servicing you, so long as those parties agree to keep this information confidential. We may also release your information when we believe release is appropriate to comply with the law, enforce our site policies, or protect ours or others rights, property, or safety. However, non-personally identifiable visitor information may be provided to other parties for marketing, advertising, or other uses.

Your Consent  
By using our site, you consent to our web site privacy policy.

Changes to our Privacy Policy  
If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes on this page.

Contacting Us  
If there are any questions regarding this privacy policy you may contact us using the information below.

http://www.nesmaairlines.com

5 El Madina Street, El Nozha El Gedida,  
Cairo  
Egypt  
info@nesmaairlines.com  
(+202) 2621 7591
